at the end of the day loneliness is just an mindset and won it as it can
归根结底，寂寞只是一种心态，并赢得了它
be difficult to graduate of feelings 'of looners'
难以摆脱“懒汉”的感觉
because the design for campaign ship is the playing ground and you me nature
因为战舰的设计是运动场，而你是我的本性
however this doesn't mean how fierce software arlo and the weekend get into
但这并不意味着Arlo和周末进入暴力软件的程度
joy or even in solitude and more positive outlook and spending
欢乐甚至孤独，更积极的前景和消费
time byars even allowing us to choose to or not
时间流逝，甚至允许我们选择
is the concept of waste lonis [Music]
是废物lonis的概念[音乐]
[Applause] youme pixar social creatures that drive
[鼓掌]驾驶的Youme皮克斯社交生物
on social interaction what diamond of human interaction
关于社会互动，人类互动的亮点
it is not the violone is can or is subjective
不是维洛隆可以还是主观的
some people spent the majority of their time malone and filoni already shows you
有些人花了大部分时间在马龙上，而filoni已经向您展示了
dumbbells fell charlie lonely despite the fact that they arthur founded by people
尽管亚瑟由人们创立，但哑铃却掉了查理一个人的寂寞
golden time there is no doubt that some people are not found wheels at all their
黄金时间毫无疑问，有些人根本找不到车轮
presence oil mix of feel alone and disconnect the path slightly in many cases
存在油的感觉，在许多情况下会感到孤独，并会稍微断开路径
wet shirt and situation that causes loneliness with the position you draw
湿衬衫和导致您绘制位置寂寞的情况
towards that situation only think of it was actually soulero
面对这种情况，只想到它实际上是seroero
bal about being alone why should we people simple
bal关于一个人，为什么我们应该简单
restless where still spinner saturday night fell in solitude for significant part
仍然不安的地方，周六晚上仍然是旋转者，大部分时间都在孤独中度过
isync the nature in the tribal and how simply this the group to survive
使部落中的自然与这个群体生存的方式同步
we would type 'we were subjected to the harness of nature it was wild animals
我们会输入“我们受到自然的束缚，那是野生动物
and sometimes dear weather conditions you do biologically
有时您在生物学上会遇到恶劣的天气情况
how to silently box tribal animals the rules of life of changed drastically
如何悄无声息地使部落动物的生活规则发生巨大变化
most modern societies de not require to mingle at all to survive these grandsons
大多数现代社会根本不需要混杂在一起就可以生存下来。
the freedom to go your own individual with everyone to for many this lack of
缺乏这种与他人在一起的自由去拥有自己的个人
necessity for you and interaction lesson in suffering to social isolation
在遭受社会孤立的过程中您的需要和互动课程
and the software that comes with it and suntec social isolation to the next
以及随附的软件和suntec社交隔离
level like the hikikomori in japan the raven
像日本的hikokomori一样的水平
withdrawn from society almost entirely how would agree that certain degree of
几乎完全退出社会
social interaction is who joyfull alfie and also and power
社会交往是谁，还有权力
oh for which he push value we most like the possibility to live to
哦，他为之推崇价值，我们最喜欢生活的可能性
rone her and kill that band too much on others
击败她并在其他人身上杀了那支乐队
despite the solidarity wim so do do with flash for pregnant soldier theo buttocks
尽管团结一致，但对怀孕的士兵西奥·臀部的闪光也是如此
tits folk at each other is better than to be close together
彼此相处的山雀比在一起相处好
de or naacp and quote from the spin suck'd right up
de或naacp并从旋转引号开始
collect the fish to gather another country then they should be the prettiest of one
收集鱼来收集另一个国家，那么它们应该是一个国家中最漂亮的
other thereby the them about them and keep on
其他从而他们关于他们，并继续
another what bider slime it would be better for
另一个什么投标人史莱姆，这将是更好的
them to for get down under in the reverse and lakes and squad
他们为了倒在倒下和湖泊和小队
pensions juicy detail ability to bio loon is an etf and dutch and prevalence
养恤金多汁的细节，对生物懒惰的能力是etf和荷兰和普遍
that most people in the plague do not have it may be easier to appreciate it
瘟疫中的大多数人没有的话，欣赏它可能会更容易
possibly lots of people or simply confect the cloth each other and heft 0
可能有很多人，或者只是使布相互沾染而堆积0
privacy whatsoever zo the basically can not enjoy solitude
隐私，根本无法享受孤独
even if they want to play teacher of show or ghost
即使他们想扮演表演老师或扮演鬼魂
bolts differences between loneliness and tall lonis
寂寞与高个子孤独之间的差异
saying that all lonis is always there or completeness and wet new thing anyone
说所有的lonis总是在那里或完整性和湿的新事物的任何人
the charm al lonis doesn't contain a value chargement slightly oil points to the
魅力lonis不包含价值押金，略有油价指向
circumstance of being alone accompanied by mutualité the bed is still good it just
独自一人陪伴床的情况还是不错的，只是
first there were gary's churn loneliness and negative undertones
首先是加里（Gary）的流浪寂寞和负面色彩
when someone is lonely this person feels a loan and saucers picasso fat wat
当一个人寂寞时，这个人就会感到借钱和飞碟毕加索的胖娃
picasso lonis has now pulled the suffering is a bad ass even the part of be in a
毕加索·洛尼斯（Picasso lonis）现在挽回了痛苦，这是一个糟糕的屁股，甚至一部分
loan your foot changer perception of being
借用脚踏开关的感知
alone we can actually enjoyed it very much
一个人，我们实际上可以非常享受
osdorp surfs that the tryin to fight wage in respond gaji-namul asia chips is not
osdorp冲浪说，在回应gaji-namul亚洲筹码的过程中，与工资抗衡的尝试不是
a longtime solution beacause relationships art temporary deep inside
长期的解决方案，因为关系艺术是暂时的
who 0 so so tryin to feel there and teens few fans or we people partner
谁0所以尝试去那里，十几岁的球迷或我们的人伴侣
will always go together with the fear of losing them as the best thing you can do
总是会害怕失去他们，因为这是您可以做的最好的事情
is to cultivate contentment in side and make it independent of the people or
是要在身边培养满足感，并使之独立于人民，或者
otherwise we can do this by bracing colonies one by one how to finish it complete how it
否则，我们可以通过一个接一个地支持殖民地来完成它，完成它的方式来做到这一点。
in or even though it sounds like your other people
甚至听起来像你的其他人
and old was toxic friend's just be cosby channel biologist and the not stay and
和老是有毒的朋友只是科斯比频道生物学家，并没有留下来，
relationship with terrible partner picas week and life with out companions
与可怕的伴侣picas周的关系以及与伴侣的生活
also be cause your content and happy with a even
也可以使您的内容满意并满意
entry don't come off so near the way paradoxically attract more people
进入市场的可能性不高，反而吸引了更多人
that I have a share or completeness lift the word lonely boy mindless or on a for
我有份或完整地举起了寂寞男孩这个词
emptiness that needs to be felt at santing external quality
在破坏外部质量时需要感觉到的空虚
or al lonis give us the opportunity to feel it off
或lonis让我们有机会感受一下
even and to be completly content in solitude
均匀而孤独地完全满足
thank you for watching [Music]
谢谢您的收看[音乐]
That
那